Connecticut Soldiers of the Revolution Correspondence
Connecticut Soldiers of the Revolution Correspondence
1838-1845
12 items (SC)
Letters addressed to the government from Troy, Watertown, and Rushford, New York as well as from Vermont and Massachusetts, concerning pension claims.
149192
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Connecticut Soldiers of the Revolution Correspondence collection contains letters written on behalf of families of Revolutionary War veterans to the Comptroller of Connecticut, requesting official certificates of service records to legalize pensions and land grants.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection contains one series, Correspondence, which is arranged chronologically.
Subject and Genre Headings
Correspondence.; Veterans -- Revolutionary War.; Revolutionary War -- Veterans.; Military history
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Purchased, 1963.
Inventory
- Correspondence
  - 24 May 1838 (Sc 226)
  - 06 Jul 1838 (Sc 226)
  - 19 Oct 1838 (Sc 226)
  - 29 Oct 1838 (Sc 226)
  - 22 Nov 1838 (Sc 226)
  - 14 Mar 1839 (Sc 226)
  - 13 Nov 1844 (Sc 226)
  - May 1845 (Sc 226)
  - 26 May 1845 (Sc 226)
  - 28 May 1845 (Sc 226)
  - 14 Jul 1845 (Sc 226)
  - 19 Jul 1845 (Sc 226)